Register of the Štefan Osuský Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1901-1974. (Box 11-31)
  - Hrabík, Martin, 1950 (Folder 21: 14)
  - Hrepta, Frank, 1950 (Folder 21: 15)
  - Hrisha, Stefan, 1941 (Folder 21: 16)
  - Hrubá, Míla, 1941 (Folder 21: 17)
  - Hrubý, Blahoslav, 1939 (Folder 21: 18)
  - Hruška, Samuel, n.d. (Folder 21: 19)
  - Hrušovsky, 1949 (Folder 21: 20)
  - Hubert, Louis-Lucien, Madame, 1939 (Folder 21: 21)
  - Hudoušek, K., 1953 (Folder 21: 22)
  - Hufnagel, L. 1939 (Folder 21: 23)
  - Hughes, John C., 1953 (Folder 21: 24)
  - Hugot-Gratry, Maurice, 1939 (Folder 21: 25)
  - Hulton Press, Ltd., 1941 (Folder 21: 26)
  - Humières, André d', 1939 (Folder 21: 27)
  - Hungarian League for the Defense of the Man and the Citizen, 1939 (Folder 21: 28)
  - Huska, Stephen, 1941 (Folder 21: 29)
  - Huyghe, René, 1939 (Folder 21: 30)
  - Information Service of Free Czechoslovakia, 1948-1964 (Folder 21: 31)
  - Ingr, Sergej, 1940 (Folder 21: 32)
  - Institut d'Etudes Européennes de Strasbourg, 1953 (Folder 21: 33)
  - Institut d'Etudes Slaves, 1939 (Folder 21: 34)
  - Institut Havrais de Sociologie Economique et de Psychologie des Peuples, 1938 (Folder 21: 35)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, 1967 (Folder 21: 36)
  - Institute of International Education, 1944 (Folder 21: 37)
  - Interdependence Council, 1956 (Folder 21: 38)
  - International Commission for War Refugees in Great Britain, 1940 (Folder 21: 39)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1956 (Folder 21: 40)
  - International Law Association, 1938 (Folder 21: 41)
  - International Movement for Atlantic Union, 1962 (Folder 21: 42)
  - International Peasant Union, 1954-1957 (Folder 21: 43)
  - L'intransigeant, 1937 (Folder 21: 44)
  - Iran. Chargé d'Affaires (France), 1939 (Folder 21: 45)
  - Iran. Légation (France), 1939 (Folder 21: 46)
  - Ireland. Legation (France) (Art Padraic o Briain), 1937 (Folder 21: 47)
  - Italy. Ambasciata (United States), 1949 (Folder 21: 48)
  - Italy. Ministero degli Affari Esteri, 1949 (Folder 21: 49)
  - Jandáček, Antonín, 1955 (Folder 21: 50)
  - Janin, M., General, 1938 (Folder 21: 51)
  - Janota, Milan, 1939 (Folder 21: 52)
  - Janouch, Svatopluk, 1950 (Folder 21: 53)
  - Janoušek, K., 1941 (Folder 21: 54)
  - Japan. Embassy (France) (Y. Sugimura), 1938 (Folder 21: 55)
  - Jardillier, Robert, 1939 (Folder 21: 56)
  - Jarka, 1943-1945 (Folder 21: 57)
  - Jaworski, J., 1943 (Folder 21: 58)
  - Jean-Lévy, 1938 (Folder 21: 59)
  - Jednota Čechoslováků v Brazilii (Czechoslovak Union in Brazil), 1956 (Folder 21: 60)
  - Jeunian, Achille, 1939 (Folder 21: 61)
  - Jevain, H., 1939 (Folder 21: 62)
  - Jílek, Bohumil, 1948-1952 (Folder 21: 63)
  - Jíra, Jaroslav, 1939-1957 (Folder 21: 64)
  - Jirkovský, 1939 (Folder 21: 65)
  - Jokl, Arnošt, 1939 (Folder 21: 66)
  - Jones, G. H., 1939 (Folder 21: 67)
  - Josko, Matěj, 1949 (Folder 21: 68)
  - Josse, Geneviève, 1939-1966 (Folder 21: 69)
  - Jouart, General, 1939 (Folder 21: 70)
  - Jouhaux, Léon, 1948 (Folder 21: 71)
  - Le Jour, 1939 (Folder 21: 72)
  - Le Jour/L'écho de Paris, 1938 (Folder 21: 73)
  - Jourdain, Francis, 1939 (Folder 21: 74)
  - Le Journal de Rouen, 1939 (Folder 21: 75)
  - Journal des débats politiques et littéraires, 1938 (Folder 21: 76)
  - Jouvenel, Claire Boas de, 1939 (Folder 21: 77)
  - Judd, J. M., 1941 (Folder 21: 78)
  - Jules-Lechat, Renée, 1939 (Folder 21: 79)
  - Kahánek, F., 1939-1940 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Kalina, Antonín Svatopluk, 1939-1948 (Folder 22: 2)
  - Kallay, Nicholas, 1958 (Folder 22: 3)
  - Kallsen, E. J., 1939 (Folder 22: 4)
  - Kapurthala, Maharaja de, 1939 (Folder 22: 5)
  - Karalus, Sylvester, 1941 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Kasparov, Karel, 1938 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Kayser, Jacques, 1939 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Keeton, George W., 1941 (Folder 22: 9)
  - Kemsley, Lord, 1941-1943 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Kennan, 1967 (Folder 22: 11)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Folder 22: 12)
  - Kerillis, Henri de, 1939 (Folder 22: 13)
  - Kerno, Yvon, 1940 (Folder 22: 14)
  - Kessler, Eric, 1941 (Folder 22: 15)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence, 1953 (Folder 22: 16)
  - King and King Estate Offices, 1942 (Folder 22: 17)
  - Klicnar, Jaromír, n.d. (Folder 22: 18)
  - Klimeš, Moric J., 1949 (Folder 22: 19)
  - Klub Dr. Milady Horákové ve Velké Britanii (Club of Milada Horáková in Great Britain), 1954 (Folder 22: 20)
  - Klub sólistů Národního divadla v Praze, 1938 (Folder 22: 21)
  - Knight, Rex, 1943 (Folder 22: 22)
  - Knox College, 1946-1948 (Folder 22: 23)
  - Kohoutová-Fiscalini, P., 1939 (Folder 22: 24)
  - Kokrda, Roman, 1956 (Folder 22: 25)
  - Kopecký, František, 1939 (Folder 22: 26)
  - Kopecký, Jaromír, 1939 (Folder 22: 27)
  - Korda, E., 1941 (Folder 22: 28)
  - Koren, Ludo, 1947-1948 (Folder 22: 29)
  - Kosner, Karel, 1948-1952 (Folder 22: 30)
  - Kotcka, Joseph, 1939 (Folder 22: 31)
  - Kotta, Nuci, 1952-1953 (Folder 22: 32)
  - Koukal, Antonín, 1938 (Folder 22: 33)
  - Koutník, Stanislav, 1952-1963 (Folder 22: 34)
  - Kovac, Juraj, 1940-1942 (Folder 22: 35)
  - Krabbe, Henning, 1941 (Folder 22: 36)
  - Krahulec, Jozef, 1941 (Folder 22: 37)
  - Králíková-Stránská, Božena, 1939 (Folder 22: 38)
  - Kratochvíl, Antonín, 1957 (Folder 22: 39)
  - Kratz, Henri, 1939 (Folder 22: 40)
  - Kreiser, W., 1939 (Folder 22: 41)
  - Kriz-Reveillaud, 1937 (Folder 22: 42)
  - Krno, I., 1939 (Folder 22: 43)
  - Kruchyne-Smith, M., 1940 (Folder 22: 44)
  - Kruh Francouzských Legionářů (The Circle of French Legionnaires), Prague, 1937 (Folder 22: 45)
  - Krumlová, Žofie, 1941 (Folder 22: 46)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik, 1959 (Folder 22: 47)
  - Kulski, 1941 (Folder 22: 48)
  - Kupka, F., 1939 (Folder 22: 49)
  - Kurdeják, Alois, 1939 (Folder 22: 50)
  - Kurtha, V. H., 1938-1939 (Folder 22: 51)
  - Kusý, Jaroslav, 1958-1968 (Folder 22: 52)
  - Kužela, Gabrik M., n.d. (Folder 22: 53)
  - Kuzma, Stanislav, 1939 (Folder 22: 54)
  - Kuzmínová, Emilie, 1940 (Folder 22: 55)
  - Kysilka, František, 1939 (Folder 22: 56)
  - Labarra, F. L. de, Madame, 1939 (Folder 22: 57)
  - Labbé, Edmond, 1938 (Folder 22: 58)
  - Laboulaye, André de, 1938-1939 (Folder 22: 59)
  - Labouret, Maurice, 1939 (Folder 22: 60)
  - Labrousse, François, 1938-1939 (Folder 22: 61)
  - Lady Margaret Hall, Oxford, 1940-1941 (Folder 22: 62)
  - Lafay, Paul, 1939 (Folder 22: 63)
  - Lafond, 1938 (Folder 22: 64)
  - Lafourche, Jean, 1950 (Folder 22: 65)
  - Lagarenne, Ferdinande de, 1941-1944 (Folder 22: 66)
  - Lambert, G. A., 1935 (Folder 22: 67)
  - Lamont, J., 1941 (Folder 22: 68)
  - Lamoureux, Lucien, 1939 (Folder 22: 69)
  - Landau, Jacob, 1937-1938 (Folder 22: 70)
  - Lanier, Th., 1939 (Folder 22: 71)
  - Lantoine, 1939-1940 (Folder 22: 72)
  - Larue-Dubost, J. L., 1939 (Folder 22: 73)
  - Lassaussois, 1939 (Folder 22: 74)
  - Lasson, General, 1938 (Folder 22: 75)
  - Lasternas, Blanche, 1938 (Folder 22: 76)
  - Latvia. Legation (United States). (Box-folder 23: 1)
    Includes a letter by Charles Zarine, Latvian Minister in London, 1949
  - Lavergne, Bernard, 1937-1939 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Lavergne, Fernand, 1940 (Folder 23: 3)
  - Lavička, Josef, 1937-1938 (Folder 23: 4)
  - Lawrence, John, 1941 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Lazard, Ch., 1938 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Leage, H., 1939 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Leagelier, L., 1939 (Folder 23: 8)
  - The League of Nations. Permanent Delegation of the Czechoslovak Republic (Délégation Permanente de la République Tchécoslovaque auprès du Secrétariat de La Société des Nations à Genève; Stálá Delegace Československé Republiky při Sekretariátu Společnosti Národů v Ženevě), 1938-1940 (Folder 23: 9)
  - Lebrun, Albert, 1927-1939. (Folder 23: 10)
    Includes a letter from Capitaine Krantz
  - Lecoutre, Georges, 1938 (Folder 23: 11)
  - Lecup, Fernand, Abbé, 1939 (Folder 23: 12)
  - Lefebvre, André, 1938 (Folder 23: 13)
  - Léger, Alexis, 1939-1940 (Folder 23: 14)
  - Legrand, Fernand, 1938 (Folder 23: 15)
  - Legras, Jules, 1937 (Folder 23: 16)
  - Leigh, A. V., 1942 (Folder 23: 17)
  - Lemann, Ch., 1938-1940 (Folder 23: 18)
  - Lemery, Henri, 1940 (Folder 23: 19)
  - Lemoine, E. F., 1939 (Folder 23: 20)
  - Lesniewski, J., 1940 (Folder 23: 21)
  - Lettrich, Jozef, 1948-1968 (Folder 23: 22)
  - Levée-Javůrková, Madeleine, 1940 (Folder 23: 23)
  - Levi, Edward H., 1958 (Folder 23: 24)
  - Levis-Mirepoix, Emmanuel de, 1938 (Folder 23: 25)
  - Leviste, Roger, Madame, 1939 (Folder 23: 26)
  - Levy, Louis, 1940 (Folder 23: 27)
  - Levy, Roger, 1938 (Folder 23: 28)
  - Lewin, S. I., 1937 (Folder 23: 29)
  - Lewy, Claude, 1940 (Folder 23: 30)
  - Lichner, Jan, 1941-1943 (Folder 23: 31)
  - Lichner, Vlastimil, 1954 (Folder 23: 32)
  - Ligue Internationale contre le Racisme et l'Antisémitisme, 1939 (Folder 23: 33)
  - Lincoln Memorial University (Tennessee), 1938 (Folder 23: 34)
  - Linhart, V. J., 1950 (Folder 23: 35)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1941 (Folder 23: 36)
  - Lisický, Karel, 1925-1957 (Folder 23: 37)
  - Lloyd George, David, 1921 (Folder 23: 38)
  - Lobbedez, 1939 (Folder 23: 39)
  - Lobkowicz, Edward Joseph, 1941-1949 (Folder 23: 40)
  - Lock, R. F., 1942-1943 (Folder 23: 41)
  - Lockart, Bruce, 1941 (Folder 23: 42)
  - Loevenstein, Karel, 1937 (Folder 23: 43)
  - Loew-Beer, 1940 (Folder 23: 44)
  - Loff, Robert, 1940 (Folder 23: 45)
  - Lokay, 1952 (Folder 23: 46)
  - Loliée, Edric, 1938 (Folder 23: 47)
  - Long de Marliave, Marguerite, 1939 (Folder 23: 48)
  - Lorin, Michel, 1939 (Folder 23: 49)
  - Loudon, John, Madame, 1938 (Folder 23: 50)
  - Louis-Dreyfus, Louis, 1938 (Folder 23: 51)
  - Low-Beer, August, 1939 (Folder 23: 52)
  - Lowe, Theo, 1938 (Folder 23: 53)
  - Lowenstein-Wetheim, Hubertus, 1939-1940 (Folder 23: 54)
  - Lowrie, Donald A., 1939 (Folder 23: 55)
  - Loze, Maurice, 1938 (Folder 23: 56)
  - Ludwig, Emil, 1940 (Folder 23: 57)
  - Lupière, André, 1938 (Folder 23: 58)
  - Lynam, T. H. R., 1941 (Folder 23: 59)
  - Lyon, Hugh, 1941 (Folder 23: 60)
  - Macadoux, L., 1940 (Folder 23: 61)
  - Machnik, František, 1937 (Folder 23: 62)
  - Macjannet Summer Camps, 1939 (Folder 23: 63)
  - Mahiu, Adolphe, 1940 (Folder 23: 64)
  - Malakhoff, A. P., 1939 (Folder 23: 65)
  - Maleville, H. de, 1938 (Folder 23: 66)
  - Malík, Josef, 1939-1945 (Folder 23: 67)
  - Mallam, Payne and Dorn, 1941 (Folder 23: 68)
  - Mallet, Alfred, 1937 (Folder 23: 69)
  - Mamatey, Victor S., 1949 (Folder 23: 70)
  - Mandelíková, Olga, 1939-1941 (Folder 23: 71)
  - Mane, Alberto, 1937 (Folder 23: 72)
  - Marckert, C. P., 1939 (Folder 23: 73)
  - Margerie, Jenny de, 1939 (Folder 23: 74)
  - Markham, R. H., 1948-1949 (Folder 23: 75)
  - Markheim, Parker and Miller, 1939 (Folder 23: 76)
  - Markovic, Ivan, 1952 (Folder 23: 77)
  - Marquet, Adrien, 1939 (Folder 23: 78)
  - Martel, René, 1939 (Folder 23: 79)
  - Martin, Louis, 1938-1939 (Folder 23: 80)
  - Martindale, Lilian, n.d. (Folder 23: 81)
  - Masaryk, Jan, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Masaryk, Tomáš Garrigue. (Folder 24: 2)
    Includes a memorandum by Heinrich Steiner on George D. Herron, 1925
  - Masaryk Society (Cambridge), 1941 (Folder 24: 3)
  - Massiani, Martial, 1939 (Folder 24: 4)
  - Massoulard, Capitaine, 1939 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Mathews, Freeman, 1945-1946 (Folder 24: 6)
  - Mathews, Walter Robert, n.d. (Folder 24: 7)
  - Mauclair, Camille, 1939 (Folder 24: 8)
  - Mawrer, Edgar, 1946 (Folder 24: 9)
  - Maxa, Prokop, 1939 (Folder 24: 10)
  - Mazel, Karel, 1941-1952 (Folder 24: 11)
  - Mazon, André, 1939 (Folder 24: 12)
  - McElroy, Charles F., 1951 (Folder 24: 13)
  - Mc Lain Freeman, N., 1939 (Folder 24: 14)
  - Médecine Mondiale, 1938 (Folder 24: 15)
  - Mege, Camille, 1939-1940 (Folder 24: 16)
  - Meggle, Armand, 1938 (Folder 24: 17)
  - Meiers, Josef, 1947-1949 (Folder 24: 18)
  - Membre, Henri, 1940 (Folder 24: 19)
  - Mercier, Ernest, 1938 (Folder 24: 20)
  - Měšťan, Jaromír, 1948-1957 (Folder 24: 21)
  - Meston of Agra, Lord, 1941-1943 (Folder 24: 22)
  - Mestrovic, Ivan, 1953 (Folder 24: 23)
  - Mettetal, René, 1939 (Folder 24: 24)
  - Metzl, Albert, 1940 (Folder 24: 25)
  - Mezorana, Milivoj, 1939 (Folder 24: 26)
  - Middle Zone Association, 1943 (Folder 24: 27)
  - Mid-European Studies Center, 1943-1953 (Folder 24: 28)
  - Migot, Georges, 1939 (Folder 24: 29)
  - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw, 1943-1959 (Folder 24: 30)
  - Milec, Leos, 1939 (Folder 24: 31)
  - Miller, Seymour, n.d. (Folder 24: 32)
  - Miltgen, Ch., 1939 (Folder 24: 33)
  - Mimin, Commandant, 1939 (Folder 24: 34)
  - Mirkine-Guetzevitch, B., 1940-1950 (Folder 24: 35)
  - Miropolska, Hélène, 1939 (Folder 24: 36)
  - Mission Evangélique Tchécoslovaque en France, 1939 (Folder 24: 37)
  - Mistouflet, Pierre, 1939 (Folder 24: 38)
  - Mládež Semilská, 1937 (Folder 24: 39)
  - Modzelewski, Jean de, 1939 (Folder 24: 40)
  - Moncek, Štefan, 1949-1973 (Folder 24: 41)
  - Monde libre, 1938 (Folder 24: 42)
  - Le Monde nouveau, 1937 (Folder 24: 43)
  - Monnet, Georges, 1939 (Folder 24: 44)
  - Monnet, Jean, 1939-1950 (Folder 24: 45)
  - Montgomery, Madeleine de, 1939 (Folder 24: 46)
  - Mora, J., 1939 (Folder 24: 47)
  - Moravec, Plukovník, 1939 (Folder 24: 48)
  - Morávek, B., 1948-1956 (Folder 24: 49)
  - Morrison, 1941 (Folder 24: 50)
  - Morton, D. G. F., 1941-1944 (Folder 24: 51)
  - Moscicki, Ignacy, 1938 (Folder 24: 52)
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1950 (Folder 24: 53)
  - Moudrý, Vladimír, 1949 (Folder 24: 54)
  - Moulton, Arthur J., 1940 (Folder 24: 55)
  - Moutet, Marius, 1939-1940 (Folder 24: 56)
  - Mruzek, Albin F., 1937 (Folder 24: 57)
  - Mudrý, Michael, 1948-1957 (Folder 24: 58)
  - Muret, Charlotte T., 1939-1949 (Folder 24: 59)
  - Murphy, Robert D., 1939-1940 (Folder 24: 60)
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1941 (Folder 24: 61)
  - Musée des Arts Décoratifs (Paris), 1940 (Folder 24: 62)
  - Nagorski, Zygmunt, 1952 (Folder 24: 63)
  - Národnie noviny (Bratislava), 1939 (Folder 24: 64)
  - Nathan, Roger, 1938 (Folder 24: 65)
  - National Alliance of Slovak Lutherans in America, 1943 (Folder 24: 66)
  - National Conference on Freedom and Peace (O. K. Armstrong), 1943-1953 (Folder 24: 67)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1956 (Folder 24: 68)
  - National Management Council, 1949 (Folder 24: 69)
  - National Slovak Society of the U.S.A. (Národný Slovenský Spolok), 1948-1950 (Folder 24: 70)
  - Navrátil, Jaroslav, 1959 (Folder 24: 71)
  - Nemcek, Andrej, 1938 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Němec, Ludvík, 1963 (Folder 25: 2)
  - Neumann, K. J., 1940 (Folder 25: 3)
  - The Never Again Association, 1943-1944 (Folder 25: 4)
  - New Commonwealth Institute, 1938-1942 (Folder 25: 5)
  - New York Times, 1948 (Folder 25: 6)
  - New-Yorské Listy, 1940 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Newnham College (Cambridge), 1941 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Nisot, Joseph, 1940 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Nitsch, Heinrich, n.d. (Folder 25: 10)
  - Nobel Peace Prize Committee, 1950 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Noel-Baker, Philip, 1941 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Notre temps, 1937 (Folder 25: 13)
  - Nouvelles d'Allemagne (Max Braun), 1938 (Folder 25: 14)
  - Nová Svoboda, 1941 (Folder 25: 15)
  - Novák, Emil, 1952 (Folder 25: 16)
  - Novák, Jaroslav, 1941 (Folder 25: 17)
  - Novák, Josef, 1940 (Folder 25: 18)
  - Novotný, Josef, 1937-1938 (Folder 25: 19)
  - Oberth, Ladislav Ivan, n.d. (Folder 25: 20)
  - The Observer, 1941 (Folder 25: 21)
  - Office de Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française. (Folder 25: 22)
    Includes correspondence with Wladimir Lefèvre d'Ormesson, 1940-1965
  - Office International du Vin, 1937-1939 (Folder 25: 23)
  - Offie, Carmel, 1943-1950 (Folder 25: 24)
  - O'Kelley de Gallagh, Countess, 1939-1940 (Folder 25: 25)
  - Olivier, General, 1940 (Folder 25: 26)
  - Ondrak, Ambroz Li, 1950 (Folder 25: 27)
  - Oppersdorff, Count, 1937 (Folder 25: 28)
  - L'ordre (Paris), 1939 (Folder 25: 29)
  - L'Ordure-Lumière (OR LU Société Anonyme), 1921-1929 (Folder 25: 30)
  - Oriel College (Oxford), 1941-1944 (Folder 25: 31)
  - Orphelins de la Région Parisienne, 1937 (Folder 25: 32)
  - Ortion, E. J., 1940 (Folder 25: 33)
  - Oscar Mason and Company, 1940 (Folder 25: 34)
  - Ossorio, Angel, 1937 (Folder 25: 35)
  - Osvětový svaz pro Slovensko v Bratislavě (Union for Slovakia in Bratislava), 1937-1938 (Folder 25: 36)
  - Ottis, Rudolf, 1939 (Folder 25: 37)
  - Outrata, Eduard, 1940 (Folder 25: 38)
  - Pacific, 1952 (Folder 25: 39)
  - Palka, Irena, 1943 (Folder 25: 40)
  - Palkovský, 1938-1942 (Folder 25: 41)
  - Palmer, Muriet, 1942 (Folder 25: 42)
  - Paris-Soir, n.d. (Folder 25: 43)
  - Passer, Kurt, 1939 (Folder 25: 44)
  - Paul-Boncour, Joseph, 1938-1939 (Folder 25: 45)
  - Paul-Cavallier, Marcel, 1938 (Folder 25: 46)
  - Paul-Marguerite, Lucie, 1939 (Folder 25: 47)
  - Pauliny-Toth, Jan, 1942-1952 (Folder 25: 48)
  - Pávek, J., 1948 (Folder 25: 49)
  - Pavel, Antonín, 1954-1956 (Folder 25: 50)
  - Pavlová, Nelia, 1939 (Folder 25: 51)
  - Pelikán, Jan, 1916 (Folder 25: 52)
  - Pergler, Charles, 1939 (Folder 25: 53)
  - Peroutka, Ferdinand, 1950 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Perquel, Jules, 1939-1940 (Folder 26: 2)
  - Perreux, Gabriel, 1938 (Folder 26: 3)
  - Perth, Earl of, 1940 (Folder 26: 4)
  - Petit, Ernest, 1940 (Folder 26: 5)
  - Petri, Charles, 1961 (Folder 26: 6)
  - Petrovitch, Sveta, 1947-1948 (Folder 26: 7)
  - Peuch, Louis, 1940 (Folder 26: 8)
  - Peysek, Antonín, 1967 (Folder 26: 9)
  - Phipps, Eric, 1940 (Folder 26: 10)
  - Picard, Camille, 1938 (Folder 26: 11)
  - Pick, Otto, 1939 (Folder 26: 12)
  - Piljan, Juraj, 1948 (Folder 26: 13)
  - Pillat, N., Madame, 1938-1939 (Folder 26: 14)
  - Planas, Virgilio, 1938 (Folder 26: 15)
  - Platts-Mill, John, 1941 (Folder 26: 16)
  - Pluhař, Josef, 1935-1958 (Folder 26: 17)
  - Polach, Jaroslav G., 1960 (Folder 26: 18)
  - Poland. Ambasada (Great Britain), 1940-1943 (Folder 26: 19)
  - Poland. Ministerstwo Informacji i Dokumentacji, 1941 (Folder 26: 20)
  - Poland. Ministerstwo Spraw Wewnetrznych, 1941 (Folder 26: 21)
  - Poland. Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych (August Zaleski), 1940-1944 (Folder 26: 22)
  - Poland. Ministerstwo Sprawiedliwosci, 1941-1944 (Folder 26: 23)
  - Poliakoff, V., 1928 (Folder 26: 24)
  - Polish Club at Oxford, 1943 (Folder 26: 25)
  - Polish Peasant Congress, 1963 (Folder 26: 26)
  - Polish Research Centre (London), 1940-1941 (Folder 26: 27)
  - Pollak, Karl, 1938 (Folder 26: 28)
  - Polloch, Joan, 1944 (Folder 26: 29)
  - Pomiane, Ed. de, 1937 (Folder 26: 30)
  - Popescu-Pion, Jean, 1926 (Folder 26: 31)
  - Portevin, Albert, 1938 (Folder 26: 32)
  - Pospíšil-Luhačovský, F., 1938 (Folder 26: 33)
  - Poznanski, 1943 (Folder 26: 34)
  - Pozze-Hennessy, R., General, 1941 (Folder 26: 35)
  - Prager Tagblatt (Paris), n.d. (Folder 26: 36)
  - Prague (Czechoslovakia). Primátor hlavního města Prahy (Mayor of the city of Prague), 1938 (Folder 26: 37)
  - Prášek, Josef, 1924-1948 (Folder 26: 38)
  - Prato, Carlo, 1938 (Folder 26: 39)
  - Právnická Jednota v Praze, 1937 (Folder 26: 40)
  - Preev, Z. N., 1944 (Folder 26: 41)
  - Prídavok, Peter, 1940 (Folder 26: 42)
  - Prívarok, Jožo, 1939 (Folder 26: 43)
  - Procházka, Adolf, 1954 (Folder 26: 44)
  - Procházka, Theodor, 1953 (Folder 26: 45)
  - Procházková, Jiřina, 1959 (Folder 26: 46)
  - Procure de St. Sulpice, Rome, 1939 (Folder 26: 47)
  - Puc, Čestmír, 1937 (Folder 26: 48)
  - Puchan, V., 1940 (Folder 26: 49)
  - Pusta, C. R., n.d. (Folder 26: 50)
  - Quatremarre, Jean, 1940 (Folder 26: 51)
  - Quentin, Maurice, 1939 (Folder 26: 52)
  - Queuille, 1938 (Folder 26: 53)
  - Quigley, Donald F., 1950 (Folder 26: 54)
  - Quirielle, P. de, 1938 (Folder 26: 55)
  - Raczkiewicz, Wladyslaw, 1943 (Folder 26: 56)
  - Raczynski, Edward, 1940 (Folder 26: 57)
  - Radigues de Chennevière, Carlos de, 1938 (Folder 26: 58)
  - Raikes, Victor, 1944 (Folder 26: 59)
  - Rappard, William, 1942 (Folder 26: 60)
  - Rašín, Miroslav, 1948-1959 (Folder 26: 61)
  - Rassemblement Mondial Contre le Racisme et l'Antisémitisme, 1938 (Folder 26: 62)
  - Raymond and Rado and Partners, 1969 (Folder 26: 63)
  - Reader's Digest, 1956 (Folder 26: 64)
  - Řehák, Edmund, 1957 (Folder 26: 65)
  - Rennaud, Paul, 1940 (Folder 26: 66)
  - Reuters (London), 1938 (Folder 26: 67)
  - Réveillaud, Jean, 1939 (Folder 26: 68)
  - La Revue de Paris, 1956 (Folder 26: 69)
  - Řezníček, Antonín, 1938 (Folder 26: 70)
  - Ribardière, Marcel, 1940 (Folder 26: 71)
  - Riou, Gaston, Madame, 1940 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Ripka, Hubert, 1949-1957 (Folder 27: 2)
  - Riss-Publicité, 1939 (Folder 27: 3)
  - Ristelhueber, 1939 (Folder 27: 4)
  - Ritter, E., 1938 (Folder 27: 5)
  - Ritz, R., 1940 (Folder 27: 6)
  - Roberts, Frank, 1945 (Folder 27: 7)
  - Robertson-Glasgow, Robert, 1942 (Folder 27: 8)
  - Rochat, Charles, 1940-1941 (Folder 27: 9)
  - Rochefoucauld, Edmée de la, 1940-1953 (Folder 27: 10)
  - Roches, Jacques de, 1937-1939 (Folder 27: 11)
  - Rodier, Camille, 1937 (Folder 27: 12)
  - Romania. Ambasada (France) (J. Gheorghiu), 1939 (Folder 27: 13)
  - Romer, Adam, 1943 (Folder 27: 14)
  - Ronus, G. A., 1943 (Folder 27: 15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1941 (Folder 27: 16)
  - Rosambert, A., 1939 (Folder 27: 17)
  - Rosamond, Robert, 1958 (Folder 27: 18)
  - Rosenberg, Harry O., 1939-1948 (Folder 27: 19)
  - Rosenthal, Leo, 1938 (Folder 27: 20)
  - Ross, David, 1941 (Folder 27: 21)
  - Rotary Club of Dorkin, 1945 (Folder 27: 22)
  - Rotary International (United Nations Rotary Outpost in London), 1943 (Folder 27: 23)
  - Roussel, Ch., 1940 (Folder 27: 24)
  - Rozehnal, Alois, 1949 (Folder 27: 25)
  - Rubrique mondaine, 1939 (Folder 27: 26)
  - Rudinský, Jozef, 1950 (Folder 27: 27)
  - Rueff, Jacques, 1956 (Folder 27: 28)
  - Ruyssen, Theodore, 1938 (Folder 27: 29)
  - Sabo, Tibor, 1950-1951 (Folder 27: 30)
  - Sachs, 1939 (Folder 27: 31)
  - Sádek, Vlastimil, 1939 (Folder 27: 32)
  - Saenger, S., 1939 (Folder 27: 33)
  - Saint Cloud Country Club, 1938 (Folder 27: 34)
  - La Saint Cyrienne (Association Amicale des Anciens Elèves de Saint-Cyr), 1939 (Folder 27: 35)
  - Saint Luke's Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1953 (Folder 27: 36)
  - Saint Martin, Comtesse de, 1932 (Folder 27: 37)
  - Saint Patrick's Rectory, 1950 (Folder 27: 38)
  - Saint Paul, Marquise de, 1939 (Folder 27: 39)
  - Saint Paul Slovak Evangelical Lutheran Church of Whiting (John S. Bradac), 1943-1954 (Folder 27: 40)
  - Saint Peter's Evangelical Lutheran Slovak Church, 1916 (Folder 27: 41)
  - Saint-Pourcain, R. de, 1939 (Folder 27: 42)
  - Saint Procopius Abbey, 1950 (Folder 27: 43)
  - Saint-René Taillandier, de, 1939-1940 (Folder 27: 44)
  - Saint Stephen's Slovak Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1950 (Folder 27: 45)
  - Saint Victor de Saint Blancard, de, 1940 (Folder 27: 46)
  - Salati-Mongellaz, L., 1938 (Folder 27: 47)
  - Salon, A., 1940 (Folder 27: 48)
  - Salon de la France d'Outre-Mer, 1940 (Folder 27: 49)
  - Sámal, Josef, 1951-1967 (Folder 27: 50)
  - Sargent, O. G., 1941 (Folder 27: 51)
  - Satora, F., 1956 (Folder 27: 52)
  - Schachman-Esseze, 1939 (Folder 27: 53)
  - Schenley Distillers, Inc., 1949 (Folder 27: 54)
  - Schlesinger, Frances, Madame, 1939 (Folder 27: 55)
  - Schmit, Maurice, 1939 (Folder 27: 56)
  - Schmitt, Pierre, 1939 (Folder 27: 57)
  - Schreiber-Crémieux, Madame, 1939 (Folder 27: 58)
  - Schulz, L., 1940 (Folder 27: 59)
  - Schwarz, František, 1945 (Folder 27: 60)
  - Sdružení Agrárních Akademiků (Association of Agrarian Academicians), 1938 (Folder 27: 61)
  - Sdružení Československých Dobrovolníků ve Francii (Alliance of Czechoslovak Volunteers in France), 1969 (Folder 27: 62)
  - Sdružení Československých Exulantů v Chicagu (Alliance of Czechoslovak Exiles in Chicago), 1953-1958 (Folder 27: 63)
  - Sdružení Demokratických Čechoslováků, Exulantů a Krajanů (Alliance of Democratic Czechoslovaks, Exiles and Countrymen), 1959 (Folder 27: 64)
  - Sdružení Zaměstnanců Zahraniční Služby v Exilu (Union of Members of the Czechoslovak Foreign Service in Exile), 1949 (Folder 27: 65)
  - Secours Démocratique aux Réfugiés (Kurt Grossman), 1939 (Folder 27: 66)
  - Sedláček, Jaromír, 1939 (Folder 27: 67)
  - Sedlák, Mirko, 1950-1956 (Folder 27: 68)
  - Šemberk, Josef, 1952 (Folder 27: 69)